smartsource.com 2010-05-27

# SmartSource Privacy Policy

SmartSource is a division of   
News America Marketing,   
a News Corporation Company.  
  
Other News Corp. Companies include: 

SmartSource Privacy Policy | Effective as of 03/12/2009

SmartSource Interactive Group (“SmartSource”) is part of the News America Group, which has adopted a set of [Privacy Principles](undefined) applicable to all its U.S.-based companies. SmartSource has implemented those Principles in this Privacy Policy, which describes how we collect, use, and share personally identifiable information (“PII”) we obtain from and about individuals located in the U.S., both online and off-line. This Privacy Policy describes the privacy practices of SmartSource. 

SmartSource.com is a general audience website and SmartSource does not knowingly collect PII from children under 13 years of age. 

From time to time SmartSource may revise this Privacy Policy to reflect industry initiatives or changes in the law, our information collection and use practices, the features of the SmartSource website, or technology. If we make revisions that change the way we collect or use your PII, those changes will be posted in this Privacy Policy and the effective date will be noted at the beginning of the Policy. Therefore, you should review it periodically so that you are up to date on our most current policies and practices. If SmartSource materially changes its practices regarding collection or use of your PII, your PII will continue to be governed by the Policy under which it was collected unless you have been provided notice of and have not objected to the change. 

This Privacy Policy is incorporated into and subject to the SmartSource website [Terms and Conditions.](undefined)

**COLLECTION:** COLLECTION OF PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION (“PII”) BY SMARTSOURCE

_General._ SmartSource collects PII in order to create or enhance our relationship with you. The types of PII that may be collected include: name, e-mail address, street address, telephone numbers, birth date, gender, salary range, and such other information as may be requested from time to time. 

When we collect PII from you it is because you are voluntarily submitting the information to us when you [1] register as a SmartSource user; [2] enter a sweepstakes, contest, or promotion, whether sponsored by us or one of our partners; [3] sign up to receive New Coupon Alerts or other offers; [4] request free samples of products; and/or [5] request assistance through the SmartSource customer service. We may also obtain PII from reputable third parties and sources including public databases. 

_Cookies._ Cookies are small bits of information that the SmartSource website places on the hard drive of your computer. Cookies remember information about your activities on the SmartSource website and enable SmartSource to make your visits to the SmartSource website more enjoyable. For example, cookies can store your password for easy logon to a site you have previously visited, or can save your preferences for a personalized home page. Information about your activities on the SmartSource website and other non-personally identifiable information about you may also be used to limit the online ads you encounter to those we believe are consistent with your interests.

Third-party advertisements displayed on the SmartSource website may also contain cookies set by Internet advertising companies or advertisers. SmartSource does not control these cookies and visitors to our website should check the privacy policy of the advertiser to see whether and how it uses cookies. See the “Notice” section below for more information on third-party advertisements. A pixel tag is a tiny images inserted in a webpage and used to record the number and types of views for that page. SmartSource may allow third party pixel tags to be present on the SmartSource website for purposes of advertising, providing services or data and statistics collection. We may also use pixel tags in order to recognize users and assess traffic patterns, and we may include pixel tags and cookies in our email messages, including newsletters, in order to count how many email messages have been opened.

SmartSource may use cookies and similar tools to relate your use of our website to PII from you or a reputable third party. For example, if you’ve asked us to send you information about our upcoming products or promotions, cookie and/or click stream data about your activities on the SmartSource website may allow us to limit the materials we send you to items we think you will find interesting, based on your prior online activities and preferences. However, if SmartSource wishes to combine your personal and cookie or click stream information in this manner, we will obtain your express affirmative consent.

You can program your computer to warn you each time a cookie is being sent or to refuse cookies completely. However, without cookies, you may not have access to certain features on the SmartSource website.

Additionally, SmartSource’s services (or third-party servers) may collect certain information about SmartSource website visitors automatically for site maintenance, optimization, security, and other legal permissible purposes. Such information may include such visitors’ IP address, browser type, date, time, and duration of visit, and particular pages viewed. 

**NOTICE:** SMARTSOURCE WILL PROVIDE YOU WITH NOTICE ABOUT ITS PII COLLECTION PRACTICES 

When you voluntarily provide PII to SmartSource, we will make sure you are informed about who is collecting the information, how and why the information is being collected, and the types of uses SmartSource will make of the information. At the time you provide your PII, SmartSource will notify you of your options regarding our use of your PII, including whether we will share it with outside companies. (See “Choice” below.) 

This Policy describes the types of other companies that may want to send you information about their products and services and therefore want to share your PII, provided you have given SmartSource permission to do so. (See “Use” below.) 

Sometimes we collect PII from consumers in manual format or off-line, such as a post card or subscription form. Providing detailed notice in those situations often proves impractical, so consumers will instead be provided with a short notice that describes how to obtain the full text of this Policy and other relevant information from us. 

When you sign up with our partners for specific services such as free samples, mailed or email newsletters, promotional offers, and product information, the partner offering the services may have access to PII and other information you provide, either because they are collecting that information along with SmartSource or because SmartSource is sharing the information with the partner. You should carefully read the privacy policy of the partner providing the services before deciding to take advantage of the service.

The SmartSource website may be linked to Internet sites operated by other companies. Some of these third party sites may be co-branded with a SmartSource logo, even though they are not operated or maintained by SmartSource. (For example, sites operated by newspapers or retailers that have a business relationship with SmartSource.) The SmartSource website may also carry advertisements from other companies. SmartSource is not responsible for the privacy practices of websites operated by third parties that are linked to our site or for the practices of third party or national Internet advertising companies. Once you’ve left the SmartSource site via such a link or by clicking on an advertisement, you should check the applicable privacy policy of the third party or advertiser site to determine how they will handle any PII they collect from you.

The SmartSource website may also be linked to sites operated by companies affiliated with SmartSource (i.e., that are part of the News America Group). Although News America Group entities adhere to the Group’s [Privacy Principles](undefined), visitors to those affiliated sites should still refer to their separate privacy policies and practices, which may differ in some respects from this Policy.

Some of the advertisements that appear on the SmartSource website are delivered to you by national Internet advertising companies. These companies utilize certain technologies to deliver advertisements and marketing messages and to collect anonymous information about your visit to the SmartSource website, including information about the ads they display, via a cookie placed in your computer that reads (or approximates) your IP address. To opt out of information collection by these companies, or to obtain information about the technologies they use or their own privacy policies, please visit: 

**CHOICE:** SMARTSOURCE WILL PROVIDE YOU WITH CHOICES ABOUT THE USE OF YOUR PII 

SmartSource will not use the PII you provide to us for purposes different from the purpose for which it was submitted, or share your PII with third parties that are not affiliated with SmartSource (i.e., not part of the News America Group), unless we obtain your permission. 

**USE:** SMARTSOURCE’S USE OF PII 

SmartSource will use the PII you provide in a manner that is consistent with this Policy. If SmartSource obtains PII from a third party, such as a business partner, our use of that information is governed by this Policy. 

We may share your PII with companies that are affiliated with us, that is are part of the News America Group of companies. And provided you have given us permission, SmartSource may share your PII with advertisers and business partners that are not affiliated with SmartSource, but would like to send you information about their products and services. For example, if you enter a sweepstakes promotion hosted by SmartSource.com, we may share the information you submit on the sweepstakes entry form with our sweepstakes partners and prize sponsors. SmartSource offers may be available on a variety of partner websites. In those instances where SmartSource offers are incorporated into a partner’s website (i.e., “micro-sited”) and where registration is required in order to receive those offers, your PII may be shared with that partner. However, you will always have the opportunity to instruct us not to share your information with third parties when PII is collected. 

SmartSource employees, agents, and contractors must have a legitimate business reason to obtain access to your PII. SmartSource may share your PII with outside contractors or agents who help us manage our information activities (i.e., sweepstakes administration, order fulfillment, or statistical analyses), but they may only use your PII to provide SmartSource with a specific service and not for any other purpose.

SmartSource may also enter into agreements with outside companies that possess the technology that allows SmartSource to customize the advertising and marketing messages you receive on our websites. Your non-PII and click stream data about your activities on our sites may be shared with these companies so this customization can be accomplished. These companies will not share your information with any third party or use it for any other purpose. Anonymous click stream and demographic information may also be shared with SmartSource’s advertisers and business partners.

There may be instances when SmartSource may disclose PII without providing you with a choice in order to protect the legal rights of SmartSource, other companies within the News America Group or their employees, agents and contractors; to protect the safety and security of visitors to our websites; to protect against fraud or for risk management purposes; or to comply with the law or legal process. In addition, if SmartSource sells all or part of its business or makes a sale or transfer of assets or is otherwise involved in a merger or business transfer, SmartSource may transfer your PII to a third party as part of that transaction. 

**SECURITY:** SMARTSOURCE PROTECTS THE SECURITY OF PII

SmartSource uses reasonable administrative, technical, personnel, and physical measures to safeguard PII in its possession against loss, theft, and unauthorized use, disclosure or modification. In addition, SmartSource uses reasonable methods to make sure that PII is accurate, up-to-date and appropriately complete. 

**ACCESS:** HOW TO ACCESS, CORRECT OR DELETE YOUR PII

Whenever possible, visitors to the SmartSource website may review the PII they have provided to us in our records. We will take reasonable steps to correct any PII a visitor informs us is incorrect. 

If you ask SmartSource to stop using your PII, SmartSource will honor that request while retaining any record of your PII that is necessary to comply with applicable federal, state, or local law. 

**REMEDIES AND COMPLIANCE:** HOW TO CONTACT SMARTSOURCE ABOUT PRIVACY CONCERNS

If you would like to communicate with SmartSource about this Privacy Policy or SmartSource’s collection and use of your PII, please contact us at: [privacy@newsamerica.com](undefined).

We can also be contacted by mail at the following address:

> Privacy Officer  
>  SmartSource Online, News America Marketing   
>  1185 Avenue of the Americas, 27th Floor   
>  New York, NY 10036
